Aqsa Iftikhar

646-764-6349

aqsa.iftikhar676@gmail.com

Skills

<u>Technical Expertise:</u> C++, Github , Python, MS Office: Excel, Word & PowerPoint , Adobe Photoshop , Visual Logic.

Language Competencies: Pashto, Urdu, Punjabi, Hindi and beginner in Italian.

<u>Extracurricular Activities:</u> Attended NY Hackathon 2019, Member of National Society of Leadership and Success and Member of Women in Technology of New York.

Education

Hunter College, City University of New York

Major: Computer Science with Bioinformatics concentration (BA)

Expected graduation December 2020

Relevant Courses

Python, Intro to C++, Discrete Structures, Software Analysis 1, Matrix Algebra, Differential equation, Macroeconomics, Calculus based Physics I, Calculus based Physics II.

Experience

Apple New York, NY

Specialist

October 2019- Present

- Dealing with customers on day to day basis by selling them different Apple products.
- Setting up customers new devices and if they encounter any problems refer them to right person.
- Troubleshooting customers different Apple products to fix the initial problems.

Napa Groups

New York, NY
Intern

January 2019

- Wrote a code for developers that was run on Jenkins.
- Wrote a C++ code for developers who were working on DevOps projects.
- Worked with developers on dockers, kubernetes, window powershell and Github.
- Made a website "Welcome to Aqsa's homepage" on nginx.

CVS Pharmacy New York, NY

Pharmacy Technician

May 2017–September 2019

- Collaborate with pharmacist at pickup to ensure customers receive quality care.
- Sort pills, create labels and review medication side effects in order to do proper packaging for medication.
- Enter insurances in the system, greet customers and ring up purchases.

Arch Global Advisors

Long Island City, NY

Intern

March 2017 – May 2017

Answered clients phone calls and forward them to specialized advisor.

- Scheduled and confirmed client appointments for advisors.
- Worked on office to make a whole month schedule for an advisor.

New York Presbyterian Queens

Queens, NY

Research Volunteer February 2016- May 2017

- Helped doctors in entering data excel from hospital database on weekly basis.
- Went to clinics with coordinators, collected notes about the patient in order to verify if we can include that patient in our study.